Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one can stop us, we rise through the storm♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع إيقافنا، نحن ننهض من خلال العاصفة♪
♪Even bleeding and broken, we'll still push on♪
♪حتى مع النزيف والكسر، سنستمر في المضي قدمًا♪
♪The earth quakes with furious might♪
♪تهتز الأرض بقوة شديدة♪
♪I'll hold your hand and charge into the light♪
♪سأمسك بيدك وأتجه نحو النور♪
♪Adventurers, a new tale begins♪
♪المغامرون، تبدأ قصة جديدة♪
♪Brave hearts in the real world win♪
♪القلوب الشجاعة تفوز في العالم الحقيقي♪
♪Sparks fly when courage collides♪
♪تتطاير الشرر عندما تلتقي الشجاعة♪
♪Burning bright, our crystal tears ignite♪
♪تحترق بشدة، وتشتعل دموعنا البلورية♪
♪Above this city we stand tall♪
♪ فوق هذه المدينة نقف شامخين ♪
♪Flying wild, we're breaking every wall♪
♪نطير في البرية، ونكسر كل الجدران♪
♪Love's grand adventure, we'll conquer it all♪
♪مغامرة الحب الكبرى، سوف نتغلب عليها جميعًا♪
=Keeping Up with Beauty= (Adapted from "The Highborn Matron Reborn as the Pitiful Heiress")
=مواكبة الجمال= (مقتبس من "السيدة النبيلة التي ولدت من جديد وريثة بائسة")
=Episode 16=
=الحلقة 16=
Chenyu.
لك.
Chenyu!
لك!
Look.
ينظر.
Zhao Muyan met with Yunyun in private!
التقى تشاو مويان مع يونيون على انفراد!
The enemy is already at our doorstep,
العدو موجود بالفعل على عتبة بابنا،
if you don't take action soon,
إذا لم تتخذ إجراءً قريبًا،
Yunyun will be taken away by someone else.
سيتم أخذ يون يون من قبل شخص آخر.
She said she chose me.
قالت أنها اختارتني.
That was then, this is now, Chenyu.
كان ذلك حينها، وهذا هو الآن، تشنيو.
Zhao Muyan is a big celebrity.
تشاو مويان هو أحد المشاهير الكبار.
He's handsome and knows how to talk.
إنه وسيم ويعرف كيف يتحدث.
He can win a girl's heart in a few words.
يستطيع الفوز بقلب الفتاة بكلمات قليلة.
I'm even his fan.
أنا حتى من معجبيه.
You want to date him?
هل تريدين مواعدته؟
No.
لا.
Chenyu,
لك،
you still have your advantages.
لا زال لديك مزاياك.
Such as?
مثل؟
For example, you're richer than him.
على سبيل المثال، أنت أغنى منه.
Wealthier than him.
أغنى منه.
And more...
و أكثر...
More prosperous than him.
أكثر ازدهارًا منه.
Prosperous.
مزدهر.
Are those three any different?
هل هؤلاء الثلاثة مختلفون؟
Anyway,
على أي حال،
what I mean is,
ما أقصده هو
you can't just sit and wait.
لا يمكنك فقط الجلوس والانتظار.
You need to show Yunyun your true feelings.
يجب عليك إظهار مشاعرك الحقيقية لـ يونيون.
True feelings.
مشاعر حقيقية.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
نعم السيد جو.
Flowing water doesn't rush to be first.
الماء الجاري لا يسارع إلى أن يكون الأول.
It strives to flow endlessly.
فهو يسعى إلى التدفق بلا نهاية.
Gu Chenyu.
قو تشينيو.
Why are you standing here?
لماذا تقف هنا؟
I...
أنا...
I'm waiting for you.
أنا في انتظارك.
Waiting for me?
في انتظاري؟
Is something wrong?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ؟
I'd like to invite you somewhere tomorrow night.
أريد أن أدعوك إلى مكان ما غدًا في الليل.
(Gu Chenyu) (I'll wait for you at the art gallery.)
(جو تشنيو) (سأنتظرك في معرض الفنون.)
Be careful, Mr. Gu.
كن حذرا، سيد جو.
(Fu Yunyun Personal Oil Painting Exhibition)
( معرض اللوحات الزيتية الشخصية للفنان فو يونيون)
Slow down, watch your step.
أبطئ، انتبه لخطواتك.
If Ms. Fu knew
لو كانت السيدة فو تعرف
that you'd collected her old paintings
أنك جمعت لوحاتها القديمة
and organized this exhibition for her,
ونظمت لها هذا المعرض،
she would be very moved.
سوف تتأثر كثيرا.
Do I look handsome?
هل أبدو وسيمًا؟
Super handsome.
وسيم للغاية.
You came, Yunyun.
لقد أتيت يا يون يون.
I know you've loved painting since you were a child.
أعلم أنك أحببت الرسم منذ أن كنت طفلاً.
I thought you might like this exhibition.
اعتقدت أن هذا المعرض قد يعجبك.
Let's go inside.
دعنا نذهب إلى الداخل.
Gu Chenyu,
قو تشينيو,
I didn't come today to see the exhibition with you.
لم آتي اليوم لرؤية المعرض معك.
I received something.
لقد تلقيت شيئا.
There are some questions I want to ask you.
هناك بعض الأسئلة التي أريد أن أسألك إياها.
Get out!
اخرج!
Uncle Fu,
العم فو
the financial situation of Jiangxing Hotel is already serious.
الوضع المالي لفندق جيانجشينغ خطير بالفعل.
Please trust me.
من فضلك ثق بي.
Give it to me,
أعطني إياها
I'll get you the best price
سأحصل لك على أفضل سعر
and help settle your debts.
ومساعدتك في تسوية ديونك.
Bah!
باه!
Who needs your fake concern?
من يحتاج إلى قلقك المزيف؟
This was all a trap you planned!
كان كل هذا فخًا خططت له!
From start to finish, you just wanted to seize Jiangxing Hotel!
من البداية إلى النهاية، كنت ترغب فقط في الاستيلاء على فندق Jiangxing!
You misunderstand me.
لقد أسأت فهمي.
I'm doing this for your sake.
انا أفعل هذا من أجلك.
Our two families have been close for so many years.
لقد كانت عائلتنا قريبتين من بعضهما البعض لسنوات عديدة.
And I thought you were always steady and reliable.
وأعتقد أنك كنت دائمًا ثابتًا وموثوقًا به.
I never thought you'd be
لم أكن أعتقد أنك ستكون
such a disappointment.
مثل هذه خيبة الأمل.
Uncle Fu, please listen to me...
العم فو، من فضلك استمع لي...
Don't push me!
لا تدفعني!
Even if I die, I'll never hand Jiangxing over to you!
حتى لو مت، لن أسلم جيانجشينغ إليك أبدًا!
Uncle Fu!
العم فو!
Get out!
اخرج!
Uncle...
عم...
This is the security footage from the corridor before my father died.
هذه لقطات أمنية من الممر قبل وفاة والدي.
He met you before his death
لقد التقى بك قبل وفاته
and had an argument with you.
وكان لي جدال معك.
Why didn't you ever tell me about it?
لماذا لم تخبرني بذلك مطلقا؟
I...
أنا...
I never told you because...
لم أخبرك أبدًا لأن...
because I was afraid you'd suspect me.
لأنني كنت خائفة من أن تشك بي.
Afraid you'd think I had something to do with his death.
أخشى أن تعتقد أن لي علاقة بوفاته.
But Uncle Fu's death wasn't my fault.
لكن موت العم فو لم يكن خطئي.
I swear it wasn't.
أقسم أنه لم يكن كذلك.
I checked the hotel's surveillance footage from that day.
لقد قمت بفحص لقطات المراقبة الخاصة بالفندق من ذلك اليوم.
I found that the footage had been hacked.
لقد وجدت أن اللقطات قد تم اختراقها.
I couldn't find anything.
لم أتمكن من العثور على أي شيء.
Hacked?
تم اختراقه؟
Gu Chenyu.
قو تشينيو.
My father couldn't have committed suicide.
لم يكن من الممكن أن ينتحر والدي .
That morning he said he'd come home for dinner.
وفي ذلك الصباح قال أنه سيعود إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء.
He promised to cook for me.
لقد وعدني بأن يطبخ لي.
Tell me, how could he have killed himself?
أخبرني كيف استطاع أن يقتل نفسه؟
You say you didn't kill him.
أنت تقول أنك لم تقتله.
Then tell me,
ثم أخبرني
who did?
من فعل؟
That day...
ذلك اليوم...
That day, I did have an argument with Uncle Fu.
في ذلك اليوم، كان لي جدال مع العم فو.
I wanted to acquire Jiangxing.
أردت الاستحواذ على Jiangxing.
But he...
لكن هو...
he refused me.
لقد رفضني.
He even kicked me out.
حتى أنه طردني.
After that, I never went back.
وبعد ذلك لم أعود أبدًا.
And then...
وثم...
Third Uncle.
العم الثالث.
I...
أنا...
Everything is just too much of a coincidence.
كل شيء هو مجرد مصادفة.
Jiangxing's cash flow broke down,
لقد انهار التدفق النقدي لشركة Jiangxing،
my father was desperate,
كان والدي يائسًا،
and you still forced him to sell the hotel.
وأجبرته أيضًا على بيع الفندق.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Then you conveniently acquired Jiangxing afterward,
ثم حصلت على Jiangxing بسهولة بعد ذلك،
and became the CEO of Gu Group.
وأصبح الرئيس التنفيذي لمجموعة Gu.
No matter what,
مهما كان الأمر،
my father's death is connected to you.
موت والدي مرتبط بك.
Yunyun.
يونيون.
I really bought Jiangxing out of good intentions.
لقد اشتريت Jiangxing بالفعل من باب النية الحسنة.
I never meant to drive Uncle Fu to his death.
لم أقصد أبدًا أن أقود العم فو إلى وفاته.
If you want Jiangxing,
إذا كنت تريد جيانغشينغ،
I can return it to you anytime.
يمكنني إعادته إليك في أي وقت.
If you still doubt Uncle Fu's death, I'll help you investigate again...
إذا كنت لا تزال تشك في وفاة العم فو، فسأساعدك في التحقيق مرة أخرى...
No need.
لا حاجة.
Gu Chenyu.
قو تشينيو.
Let's get a divorce.
دعونا نحصل على الطلاق.
Yunyun.
يونيون.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
we're completely done.
لقد انتهينا تماما.
No more ties between us.
لم يعد هناك أي روابط بيننا.
Yunyun!
يونيون!
♪Words I can't say linger on my tongue♪
♪الكلمات التي لا أستطيع قولها تبقى على لساني♪
♪Each time you're near, my heartbeat runs♪
♪في كل مرة تكون بالقرب، ينبض قلبي♪
♪Cold nights glow with gentle stars above♪
♪الليالي الباردة تتوهج بالنجوم اللطيفة في الأعلى♪
♪My silent thoughts stretch long like dreams of love♪
♪أفكاري الصامتة تمتد طويلاً مثل أحلام الحب♪
♪How do I hide these feelings so faint and shy♪
♪كيف أخفي هذه المشاعر بهذا القدر من الخجل والضعف♪
♪When I meet you again, warmth flows quietly by♪
♪عندما ألتقي بك مرة أخرى، يتدفق الدفء بهدوء♪
♪My eyes can't help but turn your way♪
♪لا يمكن لعيني إلا أن تتجه نحوك♪
♪I close them tight, pretending all is the same♪
♪أغلقهم بإحكام، وأتظاهر بأن كل شيء متشابه♪
♪The wind brushes softly by♪
♪تمر الرياح برفق♪
♪Carrying half of my sigh♪
♪أحمل نصف تنهيدة♪
♪I walk a while, then glance behind♪
♪أمشي لفترة، ثم أنظر خلفي♪
♪You bring back warmth I thought I'd lost♪
♪لقد أعادت لي الدفء الذي اعتقدت أنني فقدته♪
♪My pain quietly thaws♪
♪يذوب ألمي بهدوء♪
♪And in silence, loneliness fades away♪
♪وفي الصمت يتلاشى الشعور بالوحدة♪
♪Because you are my light in the dark♪
♪لأنك نوري في الظلام♪
♪I'll be your sun when winter feels too hard♪
♪سأكون شمسك عندما يصبح الشتاء قاسيًا جدًا♪
♪We shine for each other through the quiet and the loneliness♪
♪نحن نتألق لبعضنا البعض من خلال الهدوء والوحدة♪
♪You are the warmest light in all my world♪
♪أنت أدفأ ضوء في عالمي كله♪